我可以带伴去参加你爸妈的结婚周年派对吗
Ross, Mon, is it okay if I bring someone to your parents' anniversary party?
- 没问题   - 好啊
- Sure.     - Yeah.
- 你要带谁去    - 派克 我们在洗衣店里认识
- Who's the guy?     - Parker, I met him at the dry cleaners.
他把浆糊放在你的外套里
Did he put a little starch in your bloomers?
是谁说的
Who said that?
不 但他真的很棒 他对生命非常狂热
No, he's really great, though. He has this incredible zest for life.
他把我当女王一样
And he treats me like a queen.
但有时他当我是顽皮女孩
Except at night, when he treats me like the naughty girl I am.
我可以致词吗
Oh, by the way, would it be okay if I give the toast this year?
即使他们20周年纪念日发生了那件事
Are you sure you want to after what happened at their 20th?
- 我真的很想   - 希望这次妈不会嘘你
- Yeah, I'd really like to.     - Hopefully this time Mom won't boo you.
对 每年都是罗斯致词 他把他们都弄哭了
Yes. Every year Ross makes the toast, and it always makes them cry.
- 今年我要把他们弄哭 - 你不知道为什么最爱罗斯吗
- This year, I'm gonna make them cry.     - You wonder why Ross is their favorite?
只要罗斯一致词 大家都会哭着拍他的背
No, really, any time Ross makes a toast, everyone cries and pats him on the back.
他们都来跟我说 "天啊 你哥哥"
And they all come up to me and say, "God, your brother."
你知道今天他们今年会怎么说吗  "天啊 你"
You know what they're gonna say this year? "God, you."
至少有个人会哭
Well, I can promise you, at least one person will be crying.
我是演员 演员随时都可以哭
I'm an actor, and any actor worth his salt can cry on cue.
- 真的吗 你做的到吗    - 你是在开玩笑吗 看着
- Really? You can do that?     - Oh, you kidding me? Watch.
你们盯着我看 我办不到
Well, I can't do it with you guys watching me.
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
- 你在做什么    - 我在写我的演讲稿
- What are you doing?     - I'm working on my toast for the party.
或许我该叫它 "2002年最佳催泪弹"
Or as I like to call it: "Sob-fest 2002."
- 你看   - 是小狗
- Hey, check this out.     - It's a dog.
那是只死狗
It's a dead dog.
琪琪在我高中时死掉了
That's Chi-Chi. She died when I was in high school.
- 你爸妈的结婚周年 你要谈一只死狗 - 那个主题不错吧
- You're gonna talk about their dead pet?     - It's good stuff, huh?
- 大家好   - 嘿
- Hi.     - Hey.
乔伊 你准备好要送我爸妈的礼物了吗
Joey? You got a present for my parents? That's so sweet.
为了纪念他们结婚35周年 我用他们的名字帮星星取名
Yeah. In honor of their 35th anniversary, I had a star named after them.
- 那真的太酷了   - 我还买了老年人的性爱宝典
- That is so cool.     - And I got them Kama Sutra for the Elderly.
- 你们有多余的缎带吗    - 当然有
- Do you guys have any extra ribbon?     - Oh, yeah, sure.
你要什么 我们有蕾丝 缎子 棉布 亚麻 条纹布 你…
What do you need? We got, uh, lace, satin, sateen, raffia, gingham, felt...
我想我的蛋蛋 应该也在这里
And I think my testicles may be in here too.
琪琪 我爱这只狗
AW. Chi-Chi. Oh, I loved this dog.
摩妮卡没办法装牙套 因为琪琪得动膝盖手术
You know, uh, Monica couldn't get braces because Chi-Chi needed knee surgery.
- 什么    - 你是骑着他跑的两百磅重大胖子
- What?     - You were the 200-pounder who rode her.
大伙们 他是派克 派克 这是…
Hey. Everybody, this is Parker. Parker, this is...
不 别告诉我 让我猜 乔伊 摩妮卡 罗斯 瑞秋…
No, wait, don't tell me. Let me guess: Joey, Monica, Ross, Rachel...
对不起 菲比没有提过你
...and I'm sorry, Phoebe didn't mention you.
钱德 我是在开玩笑 你已经是我的最爱了
Chandler, I'm kidding. Already you're my favorite.
- 跟我谈谈你的事   - 事实上 我们该走了
- Tell me a little about yourselves.     - Uh, actually, we should get going.
典型的罗斯
Classic Ross.
瑞秋 你好漂亮 我可以吗
Rachel, Rachel, look how you glow. May I?
我想你已经不请自来了
I think you already are.
瑞秋 你体内孕育着一个小生命
Rachel, you have life growing inside you.
有什么更神奇… 一张狗照片 这是谁的狗
Is there anything more miraculous... Ooh, a picture of a dog. Whose is this?
那是我以前养的狗 他在好几年前过世了
That's my old dog. He passed away years ago.
至少你很幸运能拥有他 贱狗 我的老朋友
Well, at least you were lucky to have him. Bow-wow, old friend. Bow-wow.
- 派对在哪里举行    - 在 马沙皮卡
- So where's the party?     - Out on the island. It's in Massapequa.
马沙皮卡 听起来像魔法 是美国原住民历史上的名胜吗
Massapequa, it sounds magical. Is it steeped in Native American history?
那里有原住民帐篷形状的艾比餐厅
Well, there is an Arby's in the shape of a tepee.
- 我拿了纸条 你拿了礼物吗   - 拿了
- I've got my notes. You got the presents?     - Yeah.
- 我拿了车钥匙   - 我们要开车吗
- I've got the car keys.     - We're driving?
- 对   - 太棒了
- Yeah.     - Aces.
- 他似乎是个好人   - 对 我很喜欢他
- So, uh, he seems like a nice guy.     - Yeah. Yeah, I like him a lot.
- 你想留晚一点搭计程车去吗  - 好吧 不然我不想去了
- You want to hang back and take a cab?     - Okay, otherwise I'm not going.
- 嘿 妈   - 这个派对真的很棒
- Hey, Mom.     - This is such a great party.
35年 太棒了 你们有什么至理名言吗
Thirty-five years. Very impressive. Do you guys have any pearls of wisdom?
- 杰克   - 为什么食物上要插着牙签
- Jack?     - Why serve food on such a sharp stick?
那是个好问题 爸爸 那是个好问题
It's a good question, Dad. It's a good question.
- 恭喜你们   - 谢谢 我们很兴奋
- Congratulations, you two.     - Thank you, we're so excited.
还要恭喜你们结婚了
And also, congratulations on your wedding.
什么
What?
- 我们能跟你们谈一下吗    - 好吧
- Can we talk to you for just a moment?     - Yeah.
这只是件小事
It's just a little thing.
我们觉得你们未婚生子真的很棒…
While we think it's simply marvelous that you're having this baby out of wedlock...
但我们的朋友没有那么开放
...some of our friends are less open-minded.
- 我们告诉他们你们结婚了   - 什么
- Which is why we told them you're married.     - What?
谢谢你们愿意配合
Thanks for going along with this.
- 我们得假装我们结婚了   - 我为了今晚必须要刮耳毛
- We have to pretend that we're married?     - Son, I had to shave my ears for tonight.
你起码可以做到这一点吧
You can do this.
- 你能相信吗    - 我知道
- Can you believe that?     - I know.
如果你要掏耳朵 最好顺便挖一下鼻子
If you're gonna do the ears, you may as well take a pass at the nose area.
我不想骗人我结婚了
No, no, I don't want to have to lie about us being married.
我也不想 但这是他们的派对 而且只有一晚而已
I know. I don't either. But it's their party, and it's one night.
我们不必说谎 我们只要不说话
We don't even have to lie. We just won't say anything.
如果有人提起 我们只要微笑点头…
If it comes up, we'll smile, we'll nod along...
- 罗斯   - 瑞秋
- Ross?     - Rachel?
嗨 丽莎阿姨 丹姨丈
Hi, Aunt Lisa. Uncle Dan.
恭喜你们怀孕 还结了婚
Congratulations on the baby and on the wedding.
- 这是个好开始   - 你们婚后还好吧
- Here's something to get you started.     - So how's marriage treating you?
- 不可思议 太棒了   - 我们喜欢结婚
- Unbelievable. It's great.     - I love marriage.
待会儿见
We'll see you later.
- 嘿   - 嗨
- Hey.     - Hi.
好漂亮的地方 好棒的夜晚
What a beautiful place. What a great night.
我得告诉你们 能跟你们一起在C宴会厅…
I have to tell you, being here with all of you in Event Room C...
我觉得好幸运 想想这里曾有过的美好时光
...I feel so lucky. To think of all the good times that have happened here.
生日 毕业舞会 犹太教成人礼 男生跟女生的
The birthdays, the proms, the mitzvahs, both bar and bat.
通通都比不上今晚 我不想忘了它
But none of it will compare with tonight. My God, I don't want to forget this moment.
我想在我心里 帮你们拍张照 喀擦
It's like I want to take a mental picture of you all. Click.
我想闪光灯没亮
I don't think the flash went off.
- 我要去男洗手间   - 我跟你一起去
- I'm gonna go find the men's room.     - I'll go with you.
有人躲在某个地方 拿着麻醉枪…
Somewhere, there is someone with a tranquilizer gun...
跟大蝴蝶网 在找那个家伙
...and a huge butterfly net looking for that man.
我也想上厕所 但我不想让他夸奖我的小弟弟
I have to go too, but I don't want him complimenting my thing.
还好我们没在车上 他发作了吗
I'm so glad we weren't in the car. Did he ever let up?
他叫长岛高速公路是"水泥奇迹"
He called the Long Island Expressway a concrete miracle.
这个房间 今晚
This room. This night.
服务生 他的鞋子 我得用心拍张照片
That waiter. His shoes. I must take a mental picture.
抱歉
Sorry.
你们在取笑派克吗
Were you guys making fun of Parker?
那得看你听到了多少
That depends, how much did you hear?
他是有点狂热 那有什么不对
Well, he's a little enthusiastic. What's wrong with that?
- 他太过火了   - 那又怎么样 我喜欢他
- It's just... It's so much.     - Well, so what? I like him.
我会取笑你们的约会对象吗 泰格 珍妮丝 蒙娜
Do I make fun of the people you've dated? Tag, Janice, Mona.
不 因为朋友不会那么做 你们想知道我的想法吗
No, because friends don't do that. But do you want my opinion?
你们的约会纪录加起来跟人渣史差不多
In my opinion, your collective dating record reads like a who's who of human crap.
- 我觉得好难过   - 我知道
- I feel terrible.     - I know.
蒙娜有哪里不好
What was wrong with Mona?
- 快打开   - 好的 宝贝
- Open it, open it, open it.     - Yeah, baby.
我们不知道你们结婚了
So we never got to hear about your wedding.
- 我们很讶异我们没有被邀请   - 不 只有父母
- We were surprised we weren't invited.     - Oh, no, it was just our parents.
婚礼的规模很小
It was a small wedding.
但很美 简单而精致
But it was beautiful. It was small, but kind of spectacular.
- 你们在哪里举行婚礼 - 在巴巴多斯悬崖上的黄昏婚礼
- Where did you have it?     - On a cliff in Barbados, at sunset.
我走上红毯时 史提夫·汪达唱着"她真美"
And Stevie Wonder sang "isn't She Lovely" as I walked down the aisle.
- 真的吗   - 对
- Really?     - Yeah.
- 史提夫是我们家的朋友   - 天啊 那真的是太棒了
- Stevie's an old family friend.     - Oh, my God. That sounds amazing.
- 我想看照片   - 对 我也是
- I'd love to see pictures.     - Yeah, so would I.
你们不会相信 安妮·莱波维兹忘了装底片
You wouldn't think that Annie Leibovitz would forget to put film in the camera.
对不起
Would you excuse us for a second?
- 你在做什么   - 什么 我又不是你
- Um, what are you doing?     - What? I'm not you.
那可能是我唯一一场婚礼
This may be the only wedding leverhave.
- 我希望它真的很棒   - 好吧
- And I want it to be amazing.     - Okay. Okay. Ooh. Ooh.
或许我该骑着哈雷机车入场
Maybe I rode in on a Harley.
罗斯 我们得编得很像真的
Okay, Ross, it has to be realistic.
你好吗 你似乎很安静
Say, uh, ahem, are you okay? You seem kind of quiet.
- 我没事 我跟你在一起   - 我跟你在一起
- No, I'm fine. I'm great. I'm with you.     - And I'm with you.
真的是太棒了
What a great time to be alive.
看看这个送盘器
Look at this plate bouncy thing.
这是个天才发明解决了端盘子的问题
What an inspired solution to man's plate-dispensing problems.
对
Mm-hm. Yeah.
- 生蚝 让我来喂你   - 你不必那么做
- Ah. Oysters. Let me feed you one.     - That's not necessary.
- 拜托   - 我不吃…
- Please?     - No, actually, I don't eat...
- 你不吃的话我绝不罢休   - 好吧
- I won't quit until you try one.     - Okay, fine, fine.
- 很好   - 它们是什么味道 我从来没吃过
- Mm. Mm-hm. Good.     - What're they like? I've never had one.
- 试试看   - 它们看起来好奇怪
- Why don't you just try one?     - Nah, they look too weird.
- 你在做什么    - 准备我的演讲
- What are you doing?     - Just going over my toast.
会让他们好好的吓一跳
Ah, those two will never know what hit them.
我等不及了 他们会痛哭流涕 他们会喘不过气来
I can't wait. They're gonna cry so hard, they'll be fighting for breath.
如果你要的话 我可以抓住他们 让你…
You know, if you want to, I could just hold them down and you could just:
我戴的蕾丝婚纱 是由比利时盲修女织的
And my veil was lace, made by blind Belgian nuns.
- 瞎眼    - 本来不是的 但这工作非常伤眼力
- Blind?     - Well, not at first, but it was intricate work.
她们说虽然她们眼睛瞎了 但这还是很值得的
And they said even though they lost their sight, it was all worth it.
- 我敢说你看起来很漂亮   - 我不知道
- I bet you looked beautiful.     - Oh, well, I don't know about that.
但有些宾客说我看起来像飞天天使
But there were some people that said I looked like a floating angel.
- 你怎么求婚的    - 对 那是个很棒的故事
- How did you propose?     - Oh, yeah, that's a great story.
事实上 我带她去看太阳系模型展
Well, um, actually, I took her to the planetarium.
我们在那里第一次约会
That's where we had our first date.
我在房里放满了她最喜欢的百合花
Um, she walked in, and I had the room filled with, uh, lilies, her favorite flower.
- 那真的太棒了   - 我还想听
- That is so sweet.     - Shh. I want to hear the rest.
佛列德·艾斯塔唱着 "你今晚的样子"…
Then Fred Astaire singing, uh, "The Way You Look Tonight"...
灯光熄了
...came on the sound system and the lights came down...
我单脚跪下
...and I got on one knee...
圆顶另一端在群星间写着
...and written across the dome, in the stars, were the words:
"你愿意嫁给我吗 "
"Will you marry me?"
戒指有我的拳头那么大
And the ring was the size of my fist.
菲比 听着…
Hey, uh, Phoebe? Look, uh...
我想道歉 好吗 我们太坏了
...I want to apologize about before, okay? We were being jerks.
派克人很好 我想多了解他
Parker's a nice guy, and I'd like to get to know him.
你最好快去找他
Then you better do it now.
- 为什么    - 因为我要杀了他
- Why?     - Because I'm gonna kill him.
- 什么    - 他对所有事都太热衷了
- What?     - You guys were right. He's just too excited about everything.
我也很热爱生命 但这是盖勒夫妇结婚35周年派对
I mean, I'm all for living life, but this is the Gellers' 35th anniversary.
就算我们扯平了 这个派对烂透了
Let's call a spade a spade. This party stinks.
我真的觉得无聊到极点
I know. I'm having the worst time.
大家排队拿食物 我拿到盘子时…
There was a 15-minute line for the buffet, and when I finally got up to the plates...
踩到一大沱鼻涕滑倒
...I slipped on a giant booger.
你确定那不是生蚝吗
Are you sure it wasn't an oyster?
有可能 我没看
I guess it could've been. I didn't really look at it.
我把它抹在钱德的外套上 拔腿就溜
I just wiped it on Chandler's coat and got the hell out of there.
我还以为他是个好人 我对他真的很期待
I just thought he was such a great guy. I was so excited about him.
嘿 你应该对他充满期待
Well, hey, you should be excited about him.
他没有什么不好的
There's nothing wrong with him. He's a good guy.
- 真的吗    - 对 你知道吗
- You think?     - Yeah, know what I think?
- 我们太悲观了   - 你说的对
- We were all just being too negative.     - You're right.
他只是在拥抱生命 我们可以跟派克学习
You're right. He's just embracing life. We could all stand to be more like Parker.
你知道吗 我就跟他一样 我是个乐观的人
You know what? I am like him. I'm a sunny, positive person.
- 事实上 你说的对   - 那是什么
- Actually, you have a little bit of an edge.     - What's that now?
- 是派克   - 看 兔子舞
- Oh, it's Parker.     - Look, the Bunny Hop.
- 我喜欢   - 是吗
- Oh, I love it.     - You do?
你在开玩笑吗 跟着音乐学动物跳舞 来吧
Are you kidding? People acting like animals to music? Come on.
好吧 该致词了
Okay, it's time for the toast.
我知道一向都是由罗斯来致词 但今年由我来
I know that normally Ross gives the toast, but this year I'm gonna do it.
不 这真的很棒
No, it's gonna be great. Really.
好的
Okay, um...
妈 爸 我结婚时…
Mom, Dad, when I got married...
我很确定
...one of the things that made me sure that I could do it...
我要以你们为榜样
...was the amazing example the two of you set for me.
为了那一点及其他事 我要感谢你们
For that, and for so many other things, I wanna say thank you.
我想或许我不常那么说…
I know I probably don't say it enough...
但我爱你们
...but I love you.
我转头一看
When I look around this room...
悲伤地想起没办法出席的人
...I'm saddened by the thought of those who could not be with us.
我亲爱的外婆 她真的很想来
Nana, my beloved grandmother, who would so want to be here.
但她来不了…
But she can't...
因为她死了
...because she's dead.
还有我们的狗 琪琪
As is our dog, Chi-Chi.
你们看他多可爱… 那是过去的事了
I mean, look how cute she is... Was.
帮我一个忙 请把这个传给我爸妈
Do me a favor, pass this to my parents.
记住他死了 好吗 他跟外婆都死了
Remember, um, she's dead, okay? Her and Nana, gone.
有谁记得…
Hey, does anybody remember when...
黛博拉·威格在"亲密关系"中得跟孩子们说再见的样子
...Debra Winger had to say goodbye to her children in Terms of Endearment?
你们没看过
Didn't see that?
没有人是影痴
No movie fans?
你们想听些悲伤的事吗
You want to hear something sad?
我在"60分钟"
Um, the other day I was watching 60 Minutes...
看到罗马尼亚孤儿院的报导…
...and there was this piece on these orphans in Romania...
他们受到忽视 以致于无法爱人
...who have been so neglected that they were incapable of love.
你们都是铁血心肠
You people are made of stone.
敬爸妈 随便啦
Here's to Mom and Dad. Whatever.
谢谢摩妮卡 那真的是太有趣了
Thank you, Monica. That was, uh, interesting.
- 那很有趣吧 杰克   - 为什么我不记得这只狗
- Wasn't it interesting, Jack?     - Why don't I remember this dog?
罗斯 你为什么不为我们致词
Ross? Why don't you give us your toast now?
不 妈 今年轮到摩妮卡了
Oh, no, Mom. It's just Monica this year.
在我们35周年派对上 你不致词吗
You're not gonna say anything? On our 35th wedding anniversary?
当然不是这样的
No, of course, um...
大伙们 我只是想…
Um, everybody? Um, ahem, I just wanted to say...
代表我的新娘瑞秋…
...uh, on behalf of my new bride, Rachel...
跟我自己说…
...and myself, um, that if...
如果我们结婚35年后 有你们一半幸福…
If in 35 years, we're half as happy as you guys are...
我们会觉得自己是全世界最幸运的人
...we'll count ourselves the luckiest people in the world.
罗斯
Oh, Ross.
希望外婆还活着 听到罗斯的致词
I just wish Nana were alive to hear Ross' toast.
天啊 这个走廊的灯光真漂亮
My God, what a fantastically well-lit hallway.
你需要喝点东西吗 譬如水跟镇静剂
Can I, um, get you something to drink, like a water and Valium?
它… 我得说这间公寓 我不知道该怎么形容
I must say, this apartment, it's...there are no words.
- 谢天谢地   - 是个天堂
- Oh, thank God.     - It's a haven.
- 位于三楼的天堂 现代伊甸园   - 我知道 我了解
- A third-floor paradise, a modern-day Eden. - Yeah, I know, I know. Uh-huh. Gotcha.
听着 我们为什么不坐下来放轻松
Listen, why don't we just, um, sit and relax,
安静地彼此依偎
you know, just be with each other quietly.
听起来很不错
That sounds great.
这是我坐过最舒服的沙发
My God, this is the most comfortable couch I've ever sat on in my entire life.
我们试试别的点子 我们来玩游戏
Let's try something else. Let's play a game.
- 我喜欢玩游戏   - 太棒了
- I love games.     - Shocking.
我们来玩…
Um, let's play the game of...
谁能最久不说话的游戏
...who can stay quiet the longest.
或层层叠
Or Jenga.
我们先玩这个 记住 先说话的人就输了
Let's play this one first, and remember, whoever talks first loses.
- 我输了 现在来玩层层叠   - 我的天啊
- I lose, now Jenga.     - Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- 哪里不对劲吗    - 你知道什么是"不对劲"吗
- Is something wrong?     - Wrong? You know the word "wrong"?
一切不是美好又神奇吗
Everything isn't perfect? Everything isn't magical?
一切不是都在发光发亮吗
Everything isn't aglow with the light of a million fairies?
那只是刹车灯 派克
They were just brake lights, Parker.
对不起 我美化了塞车
Well, excuse me for putting a good spin on a traffic jam.
你不必美化所有事
But you don't have to put a good spin on everything.
抱歉 我是个乐观的人
I'm sorry. That's who I am. I'm a positive person.
不 我是个乐观的人
No, I'm a positive person.
你像吃抗忧郁药的圣诞老人
You are like Santa Claus on Prozac.
在迪士尼乐园被上
At Disneyland, getting laid.
你要我悲观吗
So, what do you want me to do? You want me to be more negative?
- 你要我不快乐吗   - 比较不快乐
- You want me to be less happy?     - Much less happy.
好吧 引用罗斯的话 "我最好走了"
Fine. Well, then to quote Ross, "I better be going."
再见
So long.
别让"全世界最棒的门" 在你出去时打到你的屁股了
Hey. Don't let the best door in the world hit you in the ass on your way out.
这是你一辈子吵过最不可思议的架吧
Isn't this the most incredible fight you've ever had in your entire life?
你坐在边车里 我们从婚礼现场走到接待处
We could've gone from the ceremony to the reception with you in the sidecar.
那行不通
Ross, it just wouldn't have been feasible.
但鸽子停在你的戒指上就没有问题
But having a dove place the ring on your finger would've been no problem.
跟你结婚真的太棒了
It was really fun being married to you tonight.
对 这四百块真好赚
Yeah, and it was the easiest 400 bucks I ever made.
- 罗斯 我能问你一件事吗    - 好
- Okay, Ross, can I, um, ask you something?     - Yeah.
- 在天文馆求婚    - 我知道 那太蠢了
- That proposal at the planetarium?     - I know, I know. It was stupid.
你在开玩笑吗 有百合花 歌跟星星
Are you kidding? With the lilies, and the song and the stars?
那真的是太棒 你是随便编的吗
It was really wonderful. Did you just make that up?
我们交往时 我想过要那么做
Uh, no, actually, I thought about it when we were going out.
那是我想跟你求婚的样子
That's how I imagined I, uh, would ask you to marry me.
哇
Wow.
要拒绝你一定很难
Well, that would've been, uh, very hard to say no to.
还好我没有那么做
Well, it's a good thing I didn't do it...
听起来那会是个昂贵的婚礼
...because it sounds like it would have been a very expensive wedding.
- 好吧 晚安   - 晚安
- Okay, good night.     - Good night.
即使边车有挡风玻璃不弄乱你的头发
Uh, even if the sidecar had a windscreen so your hair wouldn't get messed up?
- 我会考虑的   - 我已经满足了
- I will think about it.     - That's all I'm asking.
好吧 够了 我放弃了
Okay, that's it. I give up.
在爸妈的40周年派对上 由你来致词
At Mom and Dad's 40th anniversary, you're the one giving the speech.
我不了解他们为什么没哭 你的致词真感人
You know, I don't understand why they didn't cry. It was a beautiful speech.
- 好了   - 你说关于真爱的事
- Oh, come on.     - Hey. That stuff you said about true love?
你说的对 我们从爸妈那里学到了很多
You were right. I mean, we did learn a lot from Mom and Dad.
琪琪在照片上调皮地笑着
And that picture of Chi-Chi with her mischievous grin.
还有外婆那一段
And what you said about Nana?
她真的会很想去参加
Oh, yeah, she really would've wanted to be there.
你知道吗
And you know what?
我想她就在场
I think she was.
天啊 罗斯 你是怎么办到的
Oh, good God, Ross, how the hell do you do it'?